The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives a magicless boy named Asta.
This brave young hero devotes blood, sweat, and tears
to becoming the next Wizard King.
Though Asta's situation is practically unheard of,
there are others residing in this kingdom
who possess at least a tiny amount of mana,
yet can barely use spells at all.
They make up a very small minority,
living their lives in the shadows.
But, like everyone else,
they do their best to survive.
My prince, I've prepared your tea.
Alright.
I'm sure it's cold by now.
Sekre, how long were you there?
How long do you think, my prince?
Sorry, I didn't see you.
That's not a problem. I'm used to it.
Why don't you take a look?
A magic item that allows mana to be stored up and distributed?
That's quite an interesting idea.
It'll help increase overall mana output,
just like the elves' magic stones can do.
Oh.
You see, there's a small population in the Clover Kingdom
who weren't blessed with much magic power.
But once this device is completed,
we'll be able to easily solve that problem for them.
Huh?
Yes.
Perhaps this will stop the discrimination all those people face.
I hope so.
Unfortunately, there are other issues I'll have to fix first.
Oh, boy. Makes my head spin.
My prince thought about the future of this kingdom more than anyone else I knew.
Still, I'm sure the burn scar that I got from him will fade as time goes by.
But the scars in my heart from enduring years of ridicule,
I'll probably have those for life.
More than that, even now that they're dead,
the flames of vengeance that engulf my soul will burn forever.
We must breach the spade kingdom at any cost,
so that we can obtain the devil's power.
The reason that woman craved revenge and started this rebellion
was because she suffered the same discrimination he was talking about back then.
It may have been 500 years,
but I'm starting to realize that this kingdom hasn't changed much at all.
So,
何度も何度も何度も目の前の今を超えるさ
何度も何度も涙を希望に変えていこう
七色の日常を進め
永遠に光れ
Shine like a diamond
天使と悪魔が交際してく
世界は
宇宙だらけさ
思い通りじゃない
そのくらいで
負ける夢はダサい
そう
何度も何度も
目の前の壁を超えるさ
良さを未来に繋げよう
七色の日常を進め
永遠に光れ
You shine like a diamond
I'm sure you know why I've called you here.
I was hoping to ask you a few questions about what happened with the Devil Believers.
Sure, we'll tell you anything.
You do it.
Okay
Thank you.
If you all are ready,
let's get started now.
I heard you had a chance to speak with their leader.
Can you tell me more about that conversation?
Ah, I see.
Those who weren't blessed with mana.
Of course that would have caused an incident like this.
Their lives have been terribly unfair.
We must put an end to the discrimination.
Why are you staring at Nero?
Oh, sorry.
Pardon me.
Lord Julius,
We've just received a message from Queen Laura Pechka of the Heart Kingdom.
Wait,what?
That's their queen,huh?
It's you three.
Oh yeah,we were just talking to the Wizard King.
I see.
And you back there.
You must be Yami Sukuhiro.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
It's nice to meet you too.
Guess she does know about me then.
You may have guessed what I'm calling about.
But I'll explain.
As I said before,
The Heart Kingdom's elite guard,
The Spirit Guardians,
Have been preparing for you all to train alongside them.
What happened to her?
It looked like she was in terrible pain.
But what caused it?
Maybe Megicula's curse is already taking over.
That's not good.
Dinro.
Huh?
What's up?
Go and check things out.
We'll handle the paperwork back here.
Be careful.
Right.
Wait,Asta?
I'm sorry.
Do you mind if she stays here with us?
Sir?
efficiently likely towards this distance.
Nano see how bad they Werner helped get?
Then maybe Megicula's curse is already taking over.
That's not good.
Dinro.
What's up?
są.
Go and check things out.we'll handle the paperwork back here.
Be careful.
Right.
B Blackbird?
I'm sorry.
Do you mind if she stays here with us?
And don't standים with us.
Asta!
Okay, then, here I go.
I believe we'll be able to communicate easier
if you change back into your human form.
Now, if you'll please follow me to the basement library,
there's something I'd like you to see.
Oh, and Marks, I need you to complete the paperwork
for their entrance to Hart.
Uh, yes, sir.
Right then, let's go!
Why are we outside the palace?
I think the queen is generating a force field made of mana,
so he wasn't able to get us inside the building!
Do not advance.
I don't know what your business is here,
but it seems that you've entered our kingdom unlawfully.
Therefore, you must be punished.
Wait, it's fine, we swear!
Our Wizard King is supposed to be contacting you.
Just give him a few minutes, would you?
Yes.
What?
The proper entry forms have been submitted from the Clover Kingdom?
I understand.
Please forgive me.
I will escort you to the Queen.
Huh.
Welcome, everyone.
Is this really the same person?
She looks a little underdressed.
Her clothes may be shabby, but they can't hide her radiant beauty!
Truly, we're in the presence of a goddess!
No, wait!
I'm a changed man!
So anyway, what brings all of you here?
Right!
I just noticed!
You don't look like you're in pain anymore.
Did you come here just to talk about my curse?
Goodness!
You tripped again?
I guess that's the water spirit.
So your stomach hurt because you ate two things for lunch that didn't agree with each other?
I tried to tell her.
Red spinach with bacon is much too rough on the digestive system.
But even her fat diet is cute!
My queen, please excuse me.
Thanks for your help.
I'd better be heading back myself.
I got stuff to do.
Heading back?
But how?
You know the answer.
No way!
I'm beat!
So it's not the curse.
That's good to hear.
Anyway, as I was saying earlier,
preparations for your training are finally complete.
And that means...
What's wrong?
My glasses are gone!
Your glasses!
You didn't know?
So she can't see?
Like at all?
Honestly, Lorpechka.
What a shame!
This is the only pair you have left!
I'm a klutz.
I always end up stepping on them, kicking them, dropping them, hitting on them.
I've gone through more glasses than I can count.
Such a waste!
And they're custom made!
Okay!
Let us help you out!
Oh, don't trouble yourself.
I think I know where they are.
Wow!
Whoa!
Is she scanning the whole kingdom?
Actually, it's only one area.
But it's probably enough.
She usually has her eye on the entire land at once.
Amazing!
Ah!
There they are!
Mugi's behind this.
I knew it!
Mugi?
Wait.
Where have I seen that thing before?
It's alive!
Whoops!
I should introduce you.
This thick-pelted lady is Big Mugi.
She is Mugi's mother.
She and little Mugi show up here at the palace pretty regularly to spend some time with me.
We're used to them just coming and going as they please.
That's weird.
Why does she have such a smug face?
It's so adorable!
The only problem with these two is that they love to stir up trouble,
so sometimes they borrow my belongings without permission.
No sweat!
I'm gonna go track down this Mugi thing and get your glasses back for you!
Easy peasy!
What?
Oh no!
You don't need to!
You guys will be helping us train soon,
so this is the least we can do to repay you for that.
I'll write if you say so.
I'm exhausted, so I'll pass.
Hang on.
If I can make a positive impression on the Queen...
No! Stop it!
Don't think about it like that, Fenral!
This is just another caster breaker curse!
Don't worry, we'll get them back.
Come on, Asta!
Alright, here we go!
That must be where the beavers live.
Found them. Let's do this.
Should be easy.
Spatial magic! Fallen Angel Gate!
Now, Fallen Angel's wing beat!
Great job! You got the glasses back!
No problem.
Don't grab them by the fur.
Beavers don't like that!
What?
Man!
Are you okay?
How'd you screw that up?
You won't get away!
That rascal!
Maybe it's about to get its comeuppance.
I'm not sure.
I can't do it!
Full of yourself, aren't ya?
That's part of what makes it so cute!
I think I've got an idea!
What is that idiot doing?
Uh, he's fishing?
Well yeah, that part is obvious.
Huh?
Hmm?
I'll be taking those!
Huh?
Interesting, the key detection method used in the Land of Sun.
I see. That explains how he located you the first time, even though I was concealing you and your mana.
Yes. It doesn't matter that he has anti-magic or whether he's at the arcane stage.
I can tell he's going to become stronger and stronger.
How about a trick?
Oh.
Nice going, Asta.
Thank you very much.
Now that I have my glasses, I'll be able to see all of your smiling faces more clearly.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh. Come see me.
It looks like you hurt your hand, you poor thing. Can you move it?
Don't worry, I'm all right.
Oh no, I can't believe I did it again. I'm very sorry.
Hang on. Can you really not see?
Huh?
You seemed fine the last time we met.
The truth is, when Laura Pechka wears her royal crown, she's using mana zone, which allows her to detect people and objects in her immediate vicinity.
It's got nothing to do with her eyesight.
So if you did that all the time, you wouldn't need to wear glasses, right?
I suppose, but it's not as though I possess an infinite supply of mana.
I need to reserve some, in case something terrible befalls us.
That's right. Especially when you consider the fact that she maintains a mana zone barrier around the border of the heart kingdom at all times.
Your majesty, I have returned.
Oh good. Your timing is impeccable.
I only hope I didn't keep you waiting too long.
No.
Glasses?
I went to collect a few fresh pears for her.
Hmph. Is that what all those are?
Yes, she can never have too many.
We went to all that trouble for nothing?
I'm sorry. I tried to dissuade you, but this is your fault.
I wouldn't be my fault.
Oh right, I guess I did volunteer.
Huh.
Well, it was still very kind of you to go to such great lengths for me. I'm so thankful.
I'll go to any lengths you want, your majesty!
Damn it! Finral, get it together!
We should return to the topic at hand.
There was a reason why it took so long to finish the preparations for your training.
Uh, hey.
What's wrong?
You do know we're over here, right?
Oh my goodness, how embarrassing!
Anyway, the reason the preparations had to be delayed is because...
We needed the Spirit Guardians to be at their very best when it was time for you to meet with them.
However, there's a limit to how many trainees they'll be able to accept.
Sounds like fun! I can't wait!
No one said you were going to be one of the trainees, dummy.
Huh?
Actually, we do need Asta and Nero to participate since they can both fight at the Arcane Stage.
Really?
Wait, you said Arcane Stage. Does that mean Captain Yami and the Wizard King too?
They're already so capable. There's probably not much that we can teach them.
And according to my observations, your captain's already found a way to reach an even higher plane of magic expertise.
Seriously?
But when?
As embarrassing as it is to admit, it appears that I've lost the key to this door.
Fortunately, I hear your magic gives you the ability to open and close things at will.
Mind helping me out?
I wonder what he wants to show me in here.
Ceiling magic. Inverse release.
That book.
You're called Nero, but your real name is Sekre, right?
I noticed a little note scribbled on this page that says Sekre is going to love this.
My prince.
You see, there's a small population in the Clover Kingdom who weren't blessed with much magic power.
But once this device is completed, we'll be able to easily solve that problem for them.
Yes. Perhaps this will stop the discrimination all those people face. I hope so.
When this was written, they probably lacked the technique to create this magic item.
So I guess no one ever finished it.
That's true.
So I've taken the liberty of sending a request to the magic item research lab at Magic Knight's headquarters to have them make it according to this blueprint.
If this thing had been built before, then perhaps this Dazu Tayak and those like her would never have thought it necessary to stage a rebellion like they did.
Those who are blessed by mana and those who aren't.
The divide between these two groups has done great damage to our land.
If we want the Clover Kingdom to prosper, then we must unite everyone in harmony.
Is something wrong?
Um, no, sir.
Hey, we're back!
No more portals today.
Good to see you.
Same to you.
What did you and the Wizard King talk about?
Not much.
You do seem a little happier.
Must have been something good.
I agree.
You have been looking kind of down in the dumps recently.
So I'm glad something cheered you up.
You were said?
You all seem happy as well.
How did your visit go?
Oh, yeah.
We got some awesome news.
Pretty soon we get to go and train with the Spirit Guardians.
And you'll be coming with us, of course.
I see.
Let's kick some butt!
All right.
My prince, it looks like your wishes are going to be carried out.
Julius Novakrona.
He truly cares about the future of the Clover Kingdom.
Perhaps even as deeply as you.
I swear, I'll become stronger so that I can protect this place we love.
I keep telling you.
Go on my way
Haleに転んで傷ついて
気づけば誰ももうどこにもいない
歪んだ世界に魔法の言葉で
光が射すなら飛びつくんだろう
今目の前に残るのは希望か
掴みかけたわずかな幸福が
まだ消せない誓い叫んでる
忘れないように叫んでる
泣きたいほど遠くだって
全然届かなくても
信じる君は赤いで前を向いている
だから枯れないように柄がって
描いた夢また歩き出せるきっと
僕を呼ぶ声だ
強い
to keep our kingdom safe.
Black Clover, page 150.
The Maiden's Challenge.
Looks like Grey and Captain Charlotte are giving it their all, too.